ettv.tv 2011-11-05

# ETTV.com 娱乐在线, Free HD VBlog Recorder, Live Chat Rooms, Video Reviews, 视频博客, 視頻聊天, 視頻分享 - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

### Our Privacy Policy

### COOKIES

Ettv.com ("ETTV") uses client-side cookies to capture information about page visits and to maintain application awareness and "state". This information is anonymous and we use this information only internally to deliver the most effective content to our visitors. ETTV uses information from the cookies to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. ETTV does not require you to accept cookies; however, some functionality on this Site and the related service may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You may also change your cookie settings in your preference options in our products and/or services, where applicable.

### Volunteered Information and How We Use It

When you sign up for an account, we collect personal information from you including your e-mail address. The information allows us to process your subscription and activate your account which may include verifying authorization of credit card usage before any purchase of the ETTV service.

ETTV is a service that fosters visual communication through a variety of means. Content owners may wish to establish a direct line of communication with viewers who post comments about their media. As a means to that end, we ask that a viewer submit their e-mail address when posting comments, which we would then include in an e-mail notification message that the content owner has an option to receive. At no time is the poster's email address visible to the public. At no time do we ever share the poster's email address with anyone other than the content owner.

When you purchase something on our site, we collect personal information from you including your credit card information and the e-mail address that corresponds to your ETTV account, and to which we will send an order confirmation. We collect this information on web pages using encryption technology to help prevent any third party from intercepting the information. We only use your credit card information for completing the purchase transaction and our billing provider saves your credit card information for recurring billing purposes. We may use the information provided by our customers to analyze product trends based on, for example, geographic and demographic factors. This analysis helps us improve the quality of our website.

When you contact us via e-mail, we may use your return e-mail address to respond when necessary or when requested to do so.

We may use the information we collect to notify you occasionally about important functionality changes to our website, new ETTV services, and special offers we believe you will find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, you may opt-out at any time. We send every promotion with explicit opt-out instructions. From time to time, we may randomly contact customers about participating in a survey about our products, services and/or website. Your feedback helps us identify customer needs, levels of satisfaction, and improve and/or develop new products and services for you and your family. These surveys are always voluntary and you may opt-out at any time.

### Information Collected in Contests

If you enter one of our contests, we will handle the data we collect according to the rules of that particular contest and those rules may differ based on where you live. We provide a privacy policy specific to each contest that you should review prior to entering the contest but in general you must be 13 years or older to participate in our contests.

### INFORMATION SHARING

ETTV does not use your personal information for purposes incompatible with those listed above. ETTV does not sell or rent personal information to a third party. ETTV will provide your e-mail address as indicated above to a content owner, credit card clearing service or security service but only upon your voluntary consent to provide such information to such third parties.

ETTV may disclose relevant information about our customers to our contractors (e.g. a customer service contractor, security service contractor, or a credit card clearing service) in order for them to provide you with ETTV services, and to better serve our customers. ETTV contractors are bound by strict contractual requirements to keep all personal information they process strictly confidential and to use such information solely on behalf of ETTV.

Also, ETTV may disclose your personal information, including, without limitation, personal information regarding customers under 13, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) satisfy an applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce applicable ETTV's Terms of Use, License or Service Agreements; (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to protect against imminent harm to rights, property or safety of ETTV, its users, or the public at large as required or permitted by law.

ETTV's Site may contain links to other Websites and products. ETTV is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites or products. Please visit the privacy policies of these third party sites in order to understand their privacy policies and data collection practices.

### OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

ETTV understands that it is a privilege to have you as a customer and is committed to protecting your personal information. In addition to the security measures described above, ETTV uses the following controls to protect your personal information:

  * use of secure connections using information when transmitted from your Web browser to ETTV;

  * use of security controls to restrict access to databases housing personally identifying information;

  * use of encryption for sensitive personal information, such as credit card numbers and user names;

  * Restrict employee access to databases containing personal information and impose confidentiality requirements upon employees who do; and

  * Bind subcontractors with contractual, technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information.

If you discover a vulnerability in a ETTV product, email: [info@ettv.com](mailto:info@ettv.com). Please include a detailed summary of the issue including the name of the product (e.g., ETTV.com) and the nature of the issue you believe you've discovered. Be sure to include an email address where we can reach you in case we need more information. ETTV will respond to your notification within a reasonable amount of time and will quickly work to fix the reported vulnerability.

### DATA INTEGRITY

ETTV processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide our improve our ETTV products or services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

### Accessing Your Information

Customers may access their account information online in order to correct discrepancies and update recordings with new contact information.

### We Are Committed To Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)

At ETTV, the safety of your children is very important to us. Consequently, ETTV does not collect, knowingly or intentionally, information from children under 13 without prior verifiable parental or guardian consent. If you are under 13 and wish to purchase items from ETTV or wish to provide personal information to ETTV in connection with this service, you must obtain your parent's or guardian's consent before you register for this service or provide ETTV with any information. ETTV must rely on parent(s) or guardian(s) to decide which materials are appropriate for children under 13 to view and children under 13 cannot change registration information, only the parent or guardian can do that. Parents or guardians should follow the procedure that they used to enable their child's registration to review, change or delete any registration information at any time. Parents or guardians, you can always ask us to review or delete any of your child's information and you can refuse to permit further collection or use of your child's information at any time by sending us a written request using the contact information set forth at the beginning of this policy.

### Updates to this Policy

As our website evolves over time or our data handling policies change, we will update this privacy policy. Changes made to this policy will be effective ten days following the posting of the new policy on the website. If we make significant changes to our data handling practices, we will make efforts to notify our active customers in other reasonable ways that may include an administrative email or other notice. This privacy policy will be governed by the laws of the State of California to the extent U.S. federal law is not applicable.

### NON-U.S. CUSTOMER INFORMATION

If you are logging on from outside the United States, the personal information you submit to ETTV will be sent to and stored in servers in our U.S. headquarters in Orange county, California, U.S.A. The personal information practices set out in this Privacy Policy apply to ETTV services, and customers worldwide.

If you are in the European Union and you choose to purchase the ETTV services, please be aware that payment for such services will be handled by [asknet AG](http://www.asknet.com/). The following data may be turned over to this company solely for the purpose of processing the payment transaction: your name, credit card number or account, and amount to be charged. You have a right to access and correct such data. To exercise these rights, or for other data privacy questions, please contact us using the contact information set forth at the beginning of this policy.

### SPECIAL NOTE TO CHILDREN

If you are under 13 years old, ask your parent or guardian BEFORE giving out any information about yourself, such as your name, age, address or e-mail address. You do not have to give any personal information about yourself. Remember, if you are under 13 you must have your parent or guardian make any changes to information given to ETTV in the past or to update your profile. If you are ever unsure about anything you are seeing on this Site or a ETTV product or service, ask your parent or guardian for help.

### SPECIAL NOTE TO PARENT'S OR GUARDIAN'S OF CHILDREN UNDER 13

ETTV may collect the name of a child, parent, or guardian and online contact information in order to obtain parental or guardian consent from parents or guardians of Children under 13 and/or to provide parental or guardian notice by providing a link to this privacy policy wherever ETTV has requested personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a visitor indicates that he/she is under the age of 13, he/she will be asked to supply a parent's or guardian's e-mail address. In this case, the parent or guardian will receive an e-mail message containing instructions on how to enable the child's registration and until the parent or guardian enables the child's registration, the account is disabled. If ETTV does not receive the parent's or guardian's consent within a reasonable time, ETTV will delete this information from its records. If and when ETTV has obtained verifiable consent from a parent or guardian, ETTV will only ask for and collect from a Child under 13 personally identifiable information that is reasonably necessary for that Child to participate in any given activity online and/or use certain ETTV's  services. ETTV may also collect this information to respond to a specific request from a Child under 13. Once ETTV responds to a request from a Child under 13, ETTV may not contact that child again and the information is deleted from our records. ETTV takes very seriously the safety of children, especially those under 13 and ETTV may also collect this information to protect that safety. If ETTV collects information to protect the safety of your child, ETTV will provide notice to you and ETTV will not use that information for any other purpose. You can always ask ETTV to review or delete any of your child's information as indicated above and you can refuse to permit further collection or use of your child's information at any time by sending us a written request at the contact information set forth at the beginning of this policy. If, however, you ask us to delete your child's information that is necessary to participate in ETTV activities or use its ETTV services, ETTV may have to ask your child not to participate in such ETTV activities or use or benefit from ETTV services.

### ENFORCEMENT

ETTV regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or ETTV's treatment of personal information by contacting us using the contact information set forth at the beginning of this policy. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is ETTV's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between ETTV and an individual.

### NO ERROR FREE PERFORMANCE

We customarily release alpha and beta versions of our products and services, which are further refined before the release of the final version. Because these products or services are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome feedback on any privacy concerns you may have, and on how to improve our products or services generally, in all stages of release. ETTV does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. ETTV shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy.
